Wow, doesn't it look great?
Yeah!
It's good, right? It's good, right?
Oh!
Of course it's good!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Let's stick with it.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
You got it?
Yeah, it's good.
You're so cute.
I must have made a mistake.
I'm off.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
I'm going to go to the park!
I'm going to enter the park!
Wow!
Ready!
Yay!
We're together again today!
Wow, yeah, put this on, Mitsuki.
I'll wear blue.
Great.
How do you want it?
I'd like to be a little more spunky.
There you go.
I'll go with red.
We're all going to enjoy the suncruz.
Oh, I'm sorry, I got it!
Let's enjoy it as much as we can.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Ahi, the mountain man, has turned into a Parisian.
A little too cool?
How wonderful, Your Highness!
So Parisian! What's the first thing we're going to do?
The Takao car. Yes, that's right.
I'm a little intimidated.
Maybe it's the best scream key in Miyagi?
Maybe? I'm looking forward to it!
I've asked for your hand once again.
Oh! There it is! Ah! It's from here!
Aah! Oh, my gosh! This is gonna be fun! Oh, man!
Oh, man! Sorry, I'm a little terrible at this.
Is he in the picture? Is he in the picture?
So, he's in the park! Oh, my God!
You guys are like, what's his name? He's so bright.
We're all cheerful people, but...
But there's a misunderstanding.
Wow! You're in!
Good job!
That's great!
You want to run?
Mitsuki's hiding.
Mitsuki's a little...
She's a little timid.
If you get in trouble, just let me know.
I will.
Hold hands.
Say something nice about how the two of you are the reason I can do this.
Oh, that's very nice.
Okay, I'll go this way.
I can't.
Just go.
We'll all go together.
Ever since we found out we were going to Fujikyu.
Fujikyu's official Youtube channel.
I've already done a lot of simulations on Fujikyu's official Youtube channel.
Oh, that's great!
I kinda know this is where I'm going to fall.
Really? I saw it in the south too.
That's what happens when you're flying high.
It doesn't stop once.
Alice, you're smiling so much.
She's the strongest one, for sure.
I'm looking forward to it.
Alice will be the first to go.
I like it here.here is good
I like the doodlebugs
It's great.
I'm going to go
Good.
I just walked in on a customer.
I haven't made it very far
No, well...
Oshi Takeuchi, you're disgusting!
It's over!
Rell disappeared in the middle of the show.
You didn't see him, did you?
I didn't see him.
One moment is so fast, that's what happens when you get your head in the clouds...
Oh no!
I really wanted to film Mizuki's reaction all the time.
It was so amazing.
Like, "Aaah!
Oh, that's good.
There it is!
I'm so excited!
Wait, there's the type where you can't stand on your own feet.
There's one that you have to be able to stand on your feet to ride.
Oh, no!
Excuse me, excuse me.
Are you okay? You've got to be brave.
Take it easy.
I'll get in. Please.
That's good.
I'm in.
My body...
My body's like this.
I'm in trouble.
Katusha, that's not good, is it?
Oh, man...
Oh, my God, Katusha!
Oh, man!
Not at all.
Now...
It's great!
Please take a look at our bug-a-doodle-doo under-joggers.
I'd like to ask you to take a look at our under-jos
I'd appreciate it if you'd take a look.
Are you filming?
The catsuit. I knew it.
You have a catsuit?
Catsuits are cute.
It's cute.
I want to keep my glasses for the rest of my life.
Glasses.
I'm good.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Who is it?
I love Pretty Cure!
I don't know who it is anymore.
Yay!
What's going on?
It's on!
It looks good on you.
Kitty Cure is the best!
CureCook!
Today's strategy meeting is over.
And I definitely want to ride the teacups.
I'll be there.
Can we go, everyone?
Teacups. Oh, no, you're wrong.
And, uh, the water thing.
Shall we flush?
Flush it, of course.
By the way, Umera, do you know it's winter?
She's sleeping like a log!
Wait a minute, she's sleeping a lot today.
Oh, look at it, look at it, look at it...
Where is it?
I found the teacups.
Oh, it's already here.
Teacups.Teacups.
It's going to be fun. Look.
I'd like to ride in a teacup.
Are you good at teacups?
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm great.
Who can't spin a teacup?
Oh, good, no problem at all.
Then, I'm great in college.
That's it.
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaahhh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Good night.
Ah, good night!
...... janken!
Ah, let me jat!
Aaaaah!
Oh, kobelim!
Too much fun!
Oh, man!
Too funny!
Look who's here!
Too funny in Tincup!
That was funny!
It's always okay.
What's wrong with tinker cups?
We are a team of screamers.
We're gonna go on a lot of rides.
Look! There it is!
He's so cute!
I love the ears or something.
I like it.
Will it ruin my hair? There.
It doesn't matter.
Fuji! It's amazing.
It's cute!
It's kinda cute.
Turn around.
Yay! He's so cute!
You have to take a picture!
Shall I put the sunglasses on sale?
Aww...
I spent so much time here and didn't buy anything at all.
Yes, I love pandas.
I recently dropped my gloves somewhere.
I don't know. It was really scary down there.
Are you okay?
It's cute.
You like this?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Coward T-shirt.
I'll take that one.
You want this one?
Yeah. - Okay.
Hey, guys.
You're all so indecisive.
You can use it like a date with Yuka.
I've worn it every 29 years, I swear.
I love it. And the screams.
My whole family loves screams.
So I'm glad I got to do this.
Do you want this one?
I'll go open it.
Fujikyu Vamil.
I saw it.
Fuji.
Wow!
Yay! Here it comes!
This is all I've been thinking about lately.
I've been thinking about.
What do you think?
Yay.
It's fun.
It's a lot of fun, isn't it?
But we just spent half an hour on this.
That's not good.
I was indecisive.I was indecisive.
I was wrong about the time and a half.
Let's go. There it is.
Let's go, Rizzo.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
It really is.
It's so pretty.
It's not often that the members and I come to an amusement park like this.
We don't get to come to amusement parks very often.
I'm so glad.
I wish I could make that sound.
Awesome.
This is an extraordinary opportunity to put more and more of the gal feeling of the recruits into the world.
I didn't think I was such a gal on the way.
Like the leaky, leaky one from the last cable thing.
Love it.
Embarrassing.
Amazing.
Isn't she so hot?
Like teleportation.
It was great.
It was fun.
It was amazing!
In the middle of the show, Mr. Furie was at this angle and Fuchi-chan was bouncing in front of him.
I didn't understand what that meant.
I didn't know what angle I was at.
It was super fun.
Let's go next time.
Thank you very much.
This is probably the scariest thing I've ever done.
This is probably the scariest one for me.
Okay, let's go to the most scary one.
Okay, I'll go to "A" or something.
You can use the hashtag "Dating Julie".
And there's Riko, too.
I wanted to be in the same class as everyone else.
You're definitely a mood-maker.
I know, I know. Here we are.
I'm going to take lots of shots of you guys looking like girlfriends today.
She's so cute.
Can you say that? This is...
Oh, my God.
For everyone's safety.
We have a knack for measuring density.
Cute. Cute.
Here we are.
Oh, one more, please.
Nice to meet you.
I'll see you later.
Thank you for understanding my wish.
It was great!
It was awesome! Super fun!
It's so scary that I think it's the scariest in Fujikyu.
It was fun.
I'm getting excited.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's bad.
It's kind of like falling backwards.
It's more like when it happens like this and you fall.
For sure.
Thank you.
Yay.
What, do you see it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wow.
Oh, which one do you want to flush?
Oh, it's yellow.
Oh, is it high?
Oh, you want the yellow one?
This could be bad.
Might be bad.
Oh, but it's all the same, right? This one.
But, I mean, isn't it slow?
It's slow.
Let's take a look.
Let's take a look at it for a second.
I can go for a ride.
I'm scared.I don't want to be scared.
I'm in the mood for a yay ride.
But I'm scared... a little bit.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm scared.
I have to get on.
Mr. Hayami, I want to watch over you.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
I'll be fine.
Thank you.
I'm really excited about this new coat of water.
I just bought it yesterday.
I can ride it in the water.
My hands are better.
It's freshly unloaded.
Almost. -Freshly dropped off at a convenience store.
This is the second time I've worn it.
I don't know.
I'm a little intimidated.
Some of the guys are scared.
Are you scared?
I think I can make it.
I think I can do it.
We need to get him on board.
I'm scared.
Oh, my God, the boat won't stop.
Whoa.
Wow.
I wonder if it's possible.
Ice cream.
I can do it, cat.
We are 2 meters away, 2 meters away
Call them to make their hands disappear
Ladies and gentlemen, the waiting time for attractions
You can check it in real time.
They just said they're all coming.
Oh, they didn't all show up?
It's just a little bit of water.
That's for sure.
Maybe it's this one, this one, this one, this one.
Now, now, now, right there, right there, right there, right there.
Hey, guys.
Guys.
You've got a big smile on your face.
Wet?
I thought you could do better than that.
How was it?
She cried.
What'd she say?
You're shaking.
Are you shaking?
I'm cold.
It's cold.
Great. Let's go get a shiver.
Let's go get a shiver.
He's cute. He's waving.
See you later.
Now do you want to flush or do you want to water it down?
Shake?
Thanks for your help. I'm sorry.
No problem at all.
It was fun.
I'm sorry I talked so much.
Surprisingly, you're not wet.
I'm kind of wet.
Look at that.
I sissed.
Oh, no.
Various polka dots.
But it's wet.
But not as wet as I thought.
Can I check your bangs?
They're totally fine.
They're relatively okay.
But wow, you're still beautiful.
Look at that.
Beautiful.
Bangs
Amazing!That's great.
That's what I'm talking about.
Why is it amazing?
Not even Mr. Takamicha could beat Alice's bangs.
You couldn't win?
Not even Mr. Koubikuruma could win.
Defeat.
If you put in the swimsuit...
I'm left with nothing but bangs.
I know, I can't help it now.
Shall I wash it off?
Thank you for your hard work.
Look at this. I flushed it.
Not too many Agis.
I flushed it.
Agisu.
The best is the sea urchin.
The caddis is the best.
They defended us.
Indeed. Water.
He protected his hair.
Agis was the most scared of all.
Surprisingly. Unexpectedly.
Surprisingly.
Oh, pizza.
Oh, let's fly.
I wonder if it's combined with Pizza.
Hey. Pizza.
I'm going to go.
Big, big equipment hands, up in the sky, let's fly!
Aah!
Aaah!
Please note that customers are not allowed to use this service.
We went inside the store.
We went inside the store!
It was so much fun!
Let's jump!
Let's play!
It was fun!
Look how much fun we had!
Look at this!
Super my time!
Isn't this crazy?
Hi, there.
I don't know.
It's always been bad.
Oh, my God.
Oh, please stop with the angles.
Thank you. You're the best.
Well, it's, like, 5:00 today.
But I was doing my makeup and stuff, and I ran out of time.
I didn't have time to do any kind of delivery.
I didn't even have breakfast.
Isn't that bad?
I had a steak bowl.
What? You ate a lot of food this morning!
But I'm hungry.
I'd be sick with potatoes if I were you.
I'm really scared.
You can't be scared?
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I sent her a message saying I'm not good at it, but I'll try.
Wow, that's huge!
I think that if you don't persevere, nothing will happen.
You're right, that sounded good right now.
Please leave the quotes out already!
I'm begging you!
Oh! Wow! Brilliant step!
He jumped!
That was amazing! I didn't know there was such a thing as grass.
To be honest, I'm not falling off, so I'm good.
It's fall or no fall, that's our problem.
You don't seem scared at all.
I'm telling you!
We're going for a ride!
Are we really going?
Let's get in line! Let's get in line! Let's do it!Line up! Let's line up! Let's do it!
It's okay! It's okay! It's okay!
We'll all ride together!
Let's go! It's okay!
I can do it! I can do it!
I'm going!
We'll all do our best!
Yay!
I'm scared! Don't say anything!
Whoa!
Come on in, Space Bookstore!
Oh, my God, it's gone. It's gone.
I'm drunk.
How was it?
Oh, my God.
A little drunk.
It was a little scary.
You're right, I'm a little drunk.
We're done. It was fun.
It was scary at first.
But now it's time for us to get scared of it.
What was that? Pray for a hit.
Oh, my God. Hit Prayer.
Oh, no!
Good luck, everyone!
I'll do my best.
I'll keep cheering for you
I want to be a hit with your support
Yuka is cute?
So cute!
The city is bright!
I'm Julie.
Yes, I'm Julie.
Emo...
Emo... Emo...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nice.
Yeah, it's nice.
It's starting to look like a Vlog.
Come here.
Say "Julico Carmela.
Julico Carmela.
My goal for today is to get on one more high-mileage car.
I'd like to get on one more.
That's right.
Let's see if we can get on it.
They're climbing up the gangway.
Here they come.
Tall car.
Look at this! Look at this!
Are you okay?
I'll do my best.
Takami car!
You gonna be okay?
That was so much fun!
I've never been so scared.
I'm so happy.
Screaming is the best!
I felt like I was screaming.
Come on, let's go!
Let's go!
Oh, my God!
Hey, hey, hey!
I wonder if there's a line.
I don't know.
He's fast!
He's really going for it.
I'm off!
If you are ready to be greeted and have a seat,
It is located next to the exit, at your feet.
On the round sticker with the cartoon on it,
Please do not wave at the stickers.
Please do not wave your hand over the round sticker with the cartoon on it,
and damage caused by falling objects,
Immobilizers are recommended,
We recommend that you
Please wait for the confirmation of your baggage in the rapid tank later.Please wait for confirmation of your shipment in the rapid tank later.
We are done.
The exhilaration was incredible.
I was incredibly happy because I got to ride so much in such a short time.
I will never forget it. I am sad that it will be over in a moment.
Let's come back. I want to go again.
Let's come again, for sure. Let's come again, all of us.
I want to go to Planet, too.
I would like to go.
Please subscribe to our channel!